net2phone.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy | net2phone

This policy applies only to the NET2PHONE Web Site and mobile app (collectively, the “Site”) and not to other companies' or organizations' sites to which we may link. By accessing the Site and using the products and services offered by Net2Phone through the Site (“Services”), you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree with any term of this Privacy Policy, you may not access or use the Site or the Services.  Net2Phone will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will revise the “updated” date at the bottom of this page.

Net2Phone is committed to respecting our customer's privacy. We may share Your personally identifiable information, in compliance with applicable law, with third parties (who have similarly restrictive privacy policies) as necessary to provide You with Services and for any other lawful business purposes.  We may also share Your personally identifiable information with our parent, subsidiaries and affiliates for marketing and other lawful business purposes.

 **  
Information About Site Visitors**

Net2Phone keeps track of the Site and pages You visit within the Site in order to determine, among other things, what pages and Services are the most popular. This data helps us determine how much You use parts of the Site so we can improve our Site, and the data may also be used to deliver customized content and advertising to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.  For example, the Site may use a technology nicknamed "cookies" that tells us how and when pages in our Site are visited, and by how many people.  You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but You can usually modify Your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If You choose to decline cookies, You may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Services or the Site. We may also use web beacons and other similar tracking technologies to monitor Site traffic, improve the Site, improve our customer service and make our Site easier to use.

 **  
Use of Third Party Advertising**

The majority of the advertisements You see on the Site are displayed by Net2Phone. In addition, Net2Phone may allow other companies, called third-party advertisers, to display advertisements while you are viewing content on the Site. We do not control the content or links that appear on those advertisements and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site.

 **  
Account Information  
**Sometimes, we may specifically ask for information about You -- such as name, age, internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer, credit card number -- in order to provide the Services to You. We may also use that information to inform You about additional products and services in which You might be interested.  In order to access the Services, You may be required to create a user ID and password to establish an account. Account information may include, but is not limited to: customer name, address, telephone number, email address, and billing and payment information. Net2Phone may also retain information about Your transactions with us or our affiliates, such as Your account balances and payment history.  Email addresses may also be used for marketing Net2Phone’s and its affiliates’ products and services.

 **Third Party Disclosure**

Net2Phone may disclose Your personal information to third parties as set forth above and/or if it is required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

(a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on Net2Phone or the Site;

(b) protect and defend the rights or property of Net2Phone and the Site; or

(c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Service, the Site, or the public.

 **  
Security Measures**

Net2Phone maintains a variety of physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to guard your personally identifiable information and CPNI. Net2Phone employs commercially accepted procedures and systems to protect against unauthorized access to our systems. Net2Phone has no control over and disclaims all responsibility for the security or privacy policies or practices of other web sites on the internet even if You visit those web sites using links from the Site.

 **  
California Privacy Rights**

California law permits You to request information concerning whether Net2Phone has disclosed Your personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.  If You wish to request further information about the entities with which we have shared Your personal information for such purposes, if any, please write us at: Net2Phone Global Services, LLC, Attention: Legal Department, 520 Broad Street, Newark, New Jersey 07102.

Updated: April 2019
